{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Brick \u0026 Stone Fireplace Installers","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40035/":{"taskOID":40035,"originalTaskOID":40035,"setID":359,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":6770,"questionDisplayText":"Will your fireplace use natural gas?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Will your fireplace use natural gas?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":1245,"questionDisplayText":"Project Type","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of project is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":1157,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Building a fireplace as part of new construction","answerDisplayText":"Building a fireplace as part of new construction","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":672,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Adding a fireplace to an existing home","answerDisplayText":"Adding a fireplace to an existing home","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5254,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Replace existing fireplace","answerDisplayText":"Replace existing fireplace","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":749,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Altering an existing fireplace","answerDisplayText":"Altering an existing fireplace","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":1246,"questionDisplayText":"Fireplace Type","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of fireplace do you want to have installed?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":1103,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Brick","answerDisplayText":"Brick","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6094,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Stone","answerDisplayText":"Stone","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6159,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Stucco","answerDisplayText":"Stucco","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6354,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Tile","answerDisplayText":"Tile","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1630,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Cooking fireplace","answerDisplayText":"Cooking fireplace","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1110,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Brick oven","answerDisplayText":"Brick oven","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3762,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Masonry barbecue/fire pit","answerDisplayText":"Masonry barbecue/fire pit","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8031,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Want recommendation","answerDisplayText":"Want recommendation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":1249,"questionDisplayText":"Selected fireplace features","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Select any of the features you would like in your fireplace.","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":2739,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Gas Insert","answerDisplayText":"Gas Insert","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1860,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Decorative/Gas logs","answerDisplayText":"Decorative/Gas logs","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2809,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Glass doors","answerDisplayText":"Glass doors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2684,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Furnace rated fireplace/insert","answerDisplayText":"Furnace rated fireplace/insert","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5143,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Remote control","answerDisplayText":"Remote control","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2946,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Heat circulating grilles","answerDisplayText":"Heat circulating grilles","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1065,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Blower","answerDisplayText":"Blower","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2384,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Fan","answerDisplayText":"Fan","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1707,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Crane (for cooking)","answerDisplayText":"Crane (for cooking)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":40001,"questionDisplayText":"Materials Provided by Homeowner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Will you provide materials for this request?","shortQuestionText":"Homeowner to provide materials?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":6770,"questionDisplayText":"Will your fireplace use natural gas?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Will your fireplace use natural gas?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":1245,"questionDisplayText":"Project Type","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of project is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":1157,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Building a fireplace as part of new construction","answerDisplayText":"Building a fireplace as part of new construction","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":672,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Adding a fireplace to an existing home","answerDisplayText":"Adding a fireplace to an existing home","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5254,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Replace existing fireplace","answerDisplayText":"Replace existing fireplace","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":749,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Altering an existing fireplace","answerDisplayText":"Altering an existing fireplace","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":1157,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Building a fireplace as part of new construction","answerDisplayText":"Building a fireplace as part of new construction","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":672,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Adding a fireplace to an existing home","answerDisplayText":"Adding a fireplace to an existing home","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5254,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Replace existing fireplace","answerDisplayText":"Replace existing fireplace","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":749,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Altering an existing fireplace","answerDisplayText":"Altering an existing fireplace","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":1246,"questionDisplayText":"Fireplace Type","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of fireplace do you want to have installed?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":1103,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Brick","answerDisplayText":"Brick","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6094,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Stone","answerDisplayText":"Stone","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6159,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Stucco","answerDisplayText":"Stucco","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6354,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Tile","answerDisplayText":"Tile","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1630,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Cooking fireplace","answerDisplayText":"Cooking fireplace","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1110,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Brick oven","answerDisplayText":"Brick oven","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3762,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Masonry barbecue/fire pit","answerDisplayText":"Masonry barbecue/fire pit","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8031,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Want recommendation","answerDisplayText":"Want recommendation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":1103,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Brick","answerDisplayText":"Brick","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6094,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Stone","answerDisplayText":"Stone","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6159,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Stucco","answerDisplayText":"Stucco","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6354,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Tile","answerDisplayText":"Tile","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1630,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Cooking fireplace","answerDisplayText":"Cooking fireplace","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1110,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Brick oven","answerDisplayText":"Brick oven","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3762,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Masonry barbecue/fire pit","answerDisplayText":"Masonry barbecue/fire pit","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8031,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Want recommendation","answerDisplayText":"Want recommendation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":1249,"questionDisplayText":"Selected fireplace features","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Select any of the features you would like in your fireplace.","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":2739,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Gas Insert","answerDisplayText":"Gas Insert","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1860,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Decorative/Gas logs","answerDisplayText":"Decorative/Gas logs","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2809,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Glass doors","answerDisplayText":"Glass doors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2684,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Furnace rated fireplace/insert","answerDisplayText":"Furnace rated fireplace/insert","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5143,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Remote control","answerDisplayText":"Remote control","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2946,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Heat circulating grilles","answerDisplayText":"Heat circulating grilles","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1065,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Blower","answerDisplayText":"Blower","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2384,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Fan","answerDisplayText":"Fan","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1707,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Crane (for cooking)","answerDisplayText":"Crane (for cooking)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":2739,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Gas Insert","answerDisplayText":"Gas Insert","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1860,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Decorative/Gas logs","answerDisplayText":"Decorative/Gas logs","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2809,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Glass doors","answerDisplayText":"Glass doors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2684,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Furnace rated fireplace/insert","answerDisplayText":"Furnace rated fireplace/insert","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5143,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Remote control","answerDisplayText":"Remote control","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2946,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Heat circulating grilles","answerDisplayText":"Heat circulating grilles","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1065,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Blower","answerDisplayText":"Blower","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2384,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Fan","answerDisplayText":"Fan","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1707,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Crane (for cooking)","answerDisplayText":"Crane (for cooking)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":40001,"questionDisplayText":"Materials Provided by Homeowner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Will you provide materials for this request?","shortQuestionText":"Homeowner to provide materials?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"__cache./api/resource/task/40035/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40035,"taskName":"Brick or Stone Fireplace - Install","taskDescription":"Install a Brick or Stone Fireplace","xmTaskDescriptor":"Brick \u0026 Stone Fireplace Installers","matchable":false,"profileable":false,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":79,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"brick stone fireplace chimney hearth","textMessagingName":"Inst Fireplace","rolloverLongDesc":"Puts in an entire masonry fireplace \u0026/or chimney where one does not already exist.","rolloverShortDesc":"Install brick, stone or block fireplace or chimney.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Install a Brick or Stone Fireplace.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Brick or Stone Fireplace Installation \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":16,"acceptGoal":4,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":4,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Brick or Stone Fireplace Install","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Brick or Stone Fireplace - Install","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Brick and Stone Fireplace Project","urlName":"Brick-or-Stone-Fireplace-Install","taskConsiderationId":3,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Brick \u0026 Stone Fireplace Installers - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | HomeAdvisor","searchKeywords":"fireplace,hearth","emcCategoryOid":-12031,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":359,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false}}